A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Press Office, Series 25 FA368
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Agency and Commission Reports, 3; 13.5 Cubic Feet
  - New York State Science & Technology Foundation, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1666)
    Annual Report, December 31, 1972
  - Temporary Commission on the New York State Court System, January 2, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1667)
  - Employment Report Relating to the State's Economy, January 8, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1668)
  - New York State Housing Finance Agency, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1669)
    Annual Report, January 28, 1973
  - New York City's Mitchell-Lama Housing Program, State Study Commission for New York City, January 30, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1670)
  - New York State Commission on Gambling, Legalized Gambling, February 1, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1671)
  - Uniform Public Employees Retirement Plan, Kinzel Commission, February 6, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1672)
  - Urban Renewal in Brownsville, February 6, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1673)
  - The Neighborhoods, The City & The Region, State Study Commission for New York City, February 13, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1674)
  - The Neighborhoods, The City & The Region, State Study Commission for New York City, February 13, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1675)
  - Council of Economic Advisors, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1676)
    Annual Report, February 15, 1973
  - Willowbrook Report, February 27, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1677)
  - Social Services in New York City, State Study Commission for New York City, March 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1678)
  - Social Services in New York City, State Study Commission for New York City, March 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1679)
  - Adirondack Park Land Use & Development Plan, March 6, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1680)
  - Higher Education in New York State, March 8, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1681)
  - Adirondack Park Private Land Use & Development Plan, March 12, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1682)
  - Governor's Commission on the Future of Horse Racing in New York State, March 15, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1683)
  - Governor's Commission on the Future of Horse Racing in New York State, March 15, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1684)
  - New York State Department of Social Services, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 1685)
    Annual Report, March 27, 1973
  - Local Government in New York, Parts I, II & Summary, March 31, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1686)
  - Local Government in New York, Parts I, II & Summary, March 31, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1687)
  - Local Government in New York, Parts I, II & Summary, March 31, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1688)
  - Statewide Master Plan for Transportation Vol. I, April 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1689)
  - Health Care Needs & the New York City Health & Hospitals Corporation, State Study Commission for New York City, April 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1690)
  - Health Care Needs & the New York City Health & Hospitals Corporation, State Study Commission for New York City, April 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1691)
  - Multi-Year Master Plan of the Department of Correctional Services, April 1, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1692)
  - Multi-Year Master Plan of the Department of Correctional Services, April 1, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1693)
  - Housing & Development Administration: A Superagency Evaluated, State Study Commission for New York City, April 3, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1694)
  - New York City: Economic Base & Fiscal Capacity, State Study Commission for New York City, April 15, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1695)
  - New York State Health & Mental Hygiene Facilities Improvement Corporation, April 23, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1696)
  - State Commission on Legislative & Judicial Salaries, April 30, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1697)
  - State Study Commission for New York City, Final Report, April 30, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1698)
  - Temporary Commission on the Powers of Local Government, May 1, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1699)
  - Temporary Commission on the Powers of Local Government, May 1, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1700)
  - Temporary Commission on the Powers of Local Government, May 1, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1701)
  - Temporary Commission on the Powers of Local Government, May 1, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1702)
  - Temporary Commission on the Powers of Local Government, May 1, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1703)
  - Temporary Commission on the Powers of Local Government, May 1, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1704)
  - Temporary Commission on the Powers of Local Government, May 1, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1705)
  - Temporary Commission on the Powers of Local Government, May 1, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1706)
  - New York State Division of Human Rights, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 1707)
    Annual Report, May 9, 1973
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Energy Efficiency in Large Buildings, May 11, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1708)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Energy Efficiency in Large Buildings, May 11, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1709)
  - Urban Development Corporation, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 1710)
    Annual Report, May 21, 1973
  - Select Committee on Correctional Institutions & Programs, April 24, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1711)
  - Interdepartmental Committee on Migrant Labor, 1972-1973 (Box 75, Folder 1712)
    Annual Report, June 6, 1973
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Appliance & Apparatus Efficiency, July 24, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1713)
  - Sunnyside Sports Complex, Interim Report, December 5, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1714)
  - Creedmoor Investigation re: Mental Patient's Housing, December 18, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1715)
  - Welfare Inspector General's Report re: Data Processing Consultants' Contracts, December 17, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1716)
- Positions and Policy Papers, 4; 2 Cubic Feet
  Subseries 4 consists of press releases and background files concerning Governor Rockefeller's stand on various issues. Prepared primarily for the 1964 and 1968 presidential campaigns, this files in this subseries also include information on other candidates' positions on the issues. There is also a 1968 staff recommendation for the Governor's position on domestic issues and a 1973 summary of his positions on major issues throughout his 15 years as governor.
  - Available Speech Material, Book 1, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 1717A)
    Memoranda, policy statements and drafts of speeches which were prepared for use in the California Presidential Campaign, but were never used.
  - Available Speech Material, Book 2, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 1717B)
  - Available Speech Material, Book 3, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 1717C)
  - Available Speech Material, Book 4, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 1717D)
  - Position on Issues, Others, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 1717E)
    Summaries of other Presidential candidates' positions; H. H. Humphrey, R. F. Kennedy, E. J. McCarthy, R. M. Nixon, R. W. Reagan.
  - Recommended Positions of the Domestic Research Staff, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1718A)
  - Position on Issues, NAR, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 1718B)
  - Policy Statements, NAR, Index, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1718C)
    A chronological index of press releases containing policy statements from the 1968 campaign.
- Political and Election Analysis Files, 5; 9 Cubic Feet
  Subseries 5 consists of computer analysis of data gathered through public opinion surveys on various issues from 1966 to 1971.
  - Analysis of Ticket-Splitters, computer printout, 1968; 1970; 4 Volumes (Box 78, Folder 1719)
  - Decision Making Information, 1970-1971 (Box 79, Folder 1720)
    Various surveys concerning contemporary issues requested by the Governor. Governor's Survey 34th Congressional District, August 1970 Governor's Survey 35th Congressional District, August 1970 Governor's Survey 39th Congressional District, August 1970 Capital District Study, September 1970
  - Decision Making Information, 1970-1971 (Box 80, Folder 1721)
    Various surveys concerning contemporary issues requested by the Governor. Capital District Study, September 1970 New York Statewide Study, October 1970 New York Bond Study-Aggregate Study, September 22, 1971 New York Bond Study-Bronx, September 27, 1971 New York Bond Study-Nassau Co., September 22, 1971 New York Bond Study-Oneida Co., September 22, 1971
  - Decision Making Information, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 1722)
    Various surveys concerning contemporary issues requested by the Governor. New York Bond Study-Oneida Co., September 22, 1971 New York Bond Study-Suffolk Co., September 22, 1971
  - Election District Priority Analysis, computer printout, 1966-1970 (Box 82, Folder 1723)
    Analysis of voting data from the 1966 and 1968 elections collected by the Rockefeller for Governor Committee. Interpretation is available, see back cover of Summary Volumes. Rockefeller Report, 1970 Nixon Report, 1970 Nixon Sequence, 1970 Summary Volume-Chenango Co., September 1970 Summary Volume-Nassau Co., September 1970 Summary Volume-Rockland Co., September 1970 Summary Volume-Tompkins Co., September 1970
  - New York State Republican Election District Analysis Reports, computer printout, 1966-1970; 6 (Box 83, Folder 1724)
    Analysis of voting data taken from the 1966 and 1968 elections. - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report for Cattaraqua, Chautauqua, Chenango, Cortland, Dutchess, Herkimer, Lewis, Onondaga, Ontario, Schenectady, and Steuban counties - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report for Columbia, Niagara, Orange, Rensselaer, Saratoga, and Tioga counties - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report for Albany, Oneida, Orleans, Schoharie, Tompkins, Ulster, Washington and Wyoming counties - New York 1968-1966 Election Analysis Report for Suffolk County - New York 1968-1966 Election Analysis Report for Westchester County - New York Republican State Committee 1968-1966 Election District Analysis for Westchester County
  - New York State Republican Election District Analysis Reports, computer printout, 1966-1970; 2 (Box 84, Folder 1725)
    Analysis of voting data taken from the 1966 and 1968 elections. - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report for Broome, Cayuga, Clinton, Delaware, Franklin, Greene, Livingston, Monroe, St. Lawrence, Scholyer, Wayne, and Yates counties - New York 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report for Alleghany, Chemung, Essex, Fulton, Genesee, Hamilton, Jefferson, Madison, Montgomery, Oswego, Otsego, Putnam, Rockland, Sullivan, and Warren counties
  - New York State Republican Election District Analysis Reports, computer printout, 1966-1970; 11 (Box 85, Folder 1726A)
    Analysis of voting data taken from the 1966 and 1968 elections. - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report Town and Ward Totals for Columbia, Niagara, Orange, Rensselaer, Saratoga, and Tioga counties - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report by Assembly District for New York City - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report by Ward for New York City - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report County Totals (A-Z) - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report Town and Ward Totals for Counties (A-B) - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report Town and Ward Totals for Counties (C) - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report Town and Ward Totals for Counties (D-G) - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report Town and Ward Totals for Counties (H-M) - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report Town and Ward Totals for Counties (N-O) - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report Town and Ward Totals for Counties (P-St) - New York State 1966-1968 Election Analysis Report Town and Ward Totals for Counties (Su-Y)
  - Political Party Statistics, computer printout, New York State, undated (Box 85, Folder 1726B)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1727)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1728)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1729)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1730)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1731)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1732)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1733)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1734)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1735)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1736)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1737)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1738)
  - County Politics Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1739)
- County Visits, 6; 1.6 Cubic Feet
  Subseries 6 documents Governor Rockefeller's tours of New York in 1962. The material includes press releases, speech transcripts, and itineraries provided to the press, as well as background information on local issues in each county prepared by the governor's staff in preparation for the tours.
  - County Trips, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1740)
    Correspondence and itineraries.
  - County Trips, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1741)
  - County Trips, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1742)
  - County Trips, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1743)
  - County Trips, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1744)
  - County Trips, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1745)
  - County Trips, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1746)
  - County Trips, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1747)
  - Regional Development Tour, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1748)
    Background and speech material for the Regional Development Tour.
  - Regional Development Tour, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1749)
  - Regional Development Tour, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1750)
  - Regional Development Tour, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1751)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1752)
    Memoranda containing background information concerning New York State counties.
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1753)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1754)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1755)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1756)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1757)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1758)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1759)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1760)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1761)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1762)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1763)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1764)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1765)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1766)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1767)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1768)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1769)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1770)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1771)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1772)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1773)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1774)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 1775)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 1776)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 1777)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 1778)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 1779)
  - Special Area Problems, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 1780)
- Recommendations to Fill U.S. Senate Seat Following Robert F. Kennedy's Assassination, 1968, 7; 2 Cubic Feet
  Letters are arranged chronologically by the date they were replied to and alphabetically by the name of the person recommended thereunder.
  Subseries 7 consists of letters from the public recommending various individuals to be appointed to fill New York State's U.S. Senate seat left vacant by the assassination of Robert F. Kennedy in June 1968.
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1781)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1782)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1783)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1784)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1785)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1786)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1787)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1788)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1789)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1790)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1791)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1792)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1793)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1794)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1795)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1796)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1797)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1798)
  - June 13 - June 24, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1799)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1800)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1801)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1802)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1803)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1804)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1805)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1806)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1807)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1808)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1809)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1810)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1811)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1812)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1813)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1814)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1815)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1816)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1817)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1818)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1819)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1820)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1821)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1822)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1823)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1824)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1825)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1826)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1827)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1828)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1829)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1830)
  - June 25 - August 20, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1831)
  - August 21 - October 21, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1832)
  - August 21 - October 21, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1833)
  - August 21 - October 21, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1834)
  - August 21 - October 21, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1835)
- Miscellaneous, 8; 1.6 Cubic Feet
  Subseries 8 consists of subject and administrative files.
  - County Data Book, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 1836)
  - Drug Abuse Proposal Materials, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 1837)
    Speeches, reports, testimonies and press releases supporting NAR's drug abuse proposal.
  - Drug Abuse Proposal Materials, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 1838)
  - Drug Abuse Proposal Materials, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 1839)
  - Drug Abuse Proposal Materials, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 1840)
  - Fact Book, New York State, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1841)
  - Friedman, Joseph, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 1842)
    Correspondence, memoranda and news clippings dealing with NAR's petition of the Soviet government to allow Joseph Friedman, a Holocaust survivor, and his family to visit his brother in the United States.
  - Goldwater vs. Rockefeller, Chicago Herald Tribune Clippings, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 1843)
  - Mail Reports, Executive Chamber, 1958-1960 (Box 89, Folder 1844)
    Tallies of the subjects of incoming correspondence.
  - Mail Reports, Executive Chamber, 1958-1960 (Box 89, Folder 1845)
  - Mailing Lists, undated (Box 89, Folder 1846)
  - Mailing Lists, undated (Box 89, Folder 1847)
  - Mailing Lists, undated (Box 89, Folder 1848)
  - Mailing Lists, undated (Box 89, Folder 1849)
  - Mailing Lists, undated (Box 89, Folder 1850)
  - New York City Sanitation Strike, Key Events, February 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1851)
    Memoranda and press releases.
  - New York City Sanitation Strike, Key Events, February 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1852)
  - Press Arrangements & Expenses, 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1853)
    Memoranda, bills, passenger lists, itineraries and press releases.
  - Press Arrangements & Expenses, 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1854)
  - Press Arrangements & Expenses, 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1855)
  - Press Arrangements & Expenses, 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1856)
  - Press Arrangements & Expenses, 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1857)
  - Press Arrangements & Expenses, 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1858)
  - Press Arrangements & Expenses, 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1859)
  - Press Arrangements & Expenses, 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1860)
  - Press Arrangements & Expenses, 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1861)
  - Press Arrangements & Expenses, 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1862)
  - Press Arrangements & Expenses, 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1863)
  - Press Arrangements & Expenses, 1959-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1864)
- Statements and Press Releases, 9; 1 Cubic Feet
  Subseries 9 is arranged alphabetically by topic.
  Subseries 9 is a collection of press releases documenting the activities of Governor Rockefeller's early tenure. The releases include announcements concerning appointments; new state programs; legislation initiated, signed, or vetoed by the Governor; the Governor's reaction to major events; and other official statements and proclamations.
  - Aging, 1961-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1865)
  - Agriculture, 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1866)
  - Anti-Discrimination, 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1867)
  - Athletic Commission, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 1868)
  - Atomic Energy, 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1869)
  - Aviation Safety, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 1870)
  - Business Climate, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1871)
  - Children, 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1872)
  - Civil Defense, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1873)
  - Civil Service, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1874)
  - Civil Rights, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 1875)
  - Clemency, 1959-1960 (Box 91, Folder 1876)
  - Conservation, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 1877)
  - Consumers, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 1878)
  - Courts, 1959-1964 (Box 91, Folder 1879)
  - Culture, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1880)
  - Democracy, 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1881)
  - Economic Growth, 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1882)
  - Education, 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1883)
  - Education - Higher, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1884)
  - Election Campaign - 1960 (Box 91, Folder 1885)
  - Elections - Local - 1961 (Box 91, Folder 1886)
  - Elections - Special, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 1887)
  - Ethics, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 1888)
  - Extradition, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1889)
  - Fiscal Affairs, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1890)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1959-1964 (Box 91, Folder 1891)
  - Foreign Trade, 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1892)
  - Government Economy, 1959-1960 (Box 91, Folder 1893)
  - Government Efficiency, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1894)
  - Harness Racing, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 1895)
  - Health, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 1896)
  - Highway Safety, 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1897)
  - Highways, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 1898)
  - Housing, 1959-1964 (Box 91, Folder 1899)
  - Investigations, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1900)
  - Juvenile Delinquency, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1901)
  - Labor - Automation, 1960-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1902)
  - Labor - Government, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 1903)
  - Labor - Management, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1904)
  - Labor - Minimum Wage - State, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 1905)
  - Latin America, 1959-1960 (Box 91, Folder 1906)
  - Law Enforcement, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 1907)
  - Legislative Program, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 1908)
  - Legislative Session, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 1909)
  - Legislative Session, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 1910)
  - Legislative Session, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 1911)
  - Legislative Session, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 1912)
  - Local Government, 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1913)
  - Mental Hygiene, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 1914)
  - National Security, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 1915)
  - New York City - Governmental Operations, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1916)
  - New York City - State Aid, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 1917)
  - New York City - Taxes, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 1918)
  - Penal Law, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 1919)